Take these back and
I tear 'em up too. Hittin' like I drive
with a cruise control.
This is Croydon,
blaze in the cold wind.
Southside living,
bare pain that I hold in. High road
life, but my heart stay frozen.
Still on my
outside.
How'd you get on at the doctor's,
by the way? Kidney stones.
Happens to the best of us.
Kitchen's just opened, lads.
We're not here to eat.
We're here to collect.
Open the till.
Do you know who protects this pub?
Is it the Trinco boys?
Well, since you're such good friends,
you can deliver a
message.
These ends
belong to Harrington now. Call it a
gift.
War it is, then.
I forget how shit Thornton Heath station is.
You sure you should leave the ends right
now? One and Twelve needs its leader.
Literally just gotta help my cuz
with some boxes.
Be back on
Monday.
Going somewhere, bruv?
Yo,
Theo, I can't make it no more.
Something came up.
Nah, they're long gone.
Fucking P Block.
They've never gone as far as Birkbeck
before. They were probing.
When they're ready to hit,
we'll know it. All right. Cool.
We'll watch the border.
They're testing cause they think we're
weak. This is why you can't leave.
I ain't gonna talk about this over
the phone.
Vultures are circling,
man. P Block attacks us in
Birkbeck.
Gift crew tries to run Trinco boys out
of South.
Old crew tries to take out One-One-Two's
top boy.
All in a couple of hours.
They're working together.
Joe was right about you. I'm with you.
What's our next steps?
P Block, Gift,
and Oak were out here making friends.
It's time we did the same.
I think us three have got shit to talk
about.
This is Croydon,
blaze in the cold wind. Yeah.
Southside living,
bare pain that I hold in. High road
life, but my heart stay frozen.
Still on my outside.
Guess Holmesdale wised up. Them working
with Trinco boys and
One-One-Two ain't a
problem.
They can't stop us now. Nothing
can.